A great way to learn a variety of
要学习各种计算机视觉技术
computer vision techniques is by building an image classifier.
最好的方法是构建一个图像分类器
A lot of what we'll focus on in this lesson is grouping image data into classes,
在本课中 我们关注的大部分内容是把图像数据归为不同类别
like humans, bikes, and cars or images taken during the day vs at night.
比如 人类、自行车、汽车或白天 vs 夜间拍摄的照片
And some of these classification tasks are quite challenging.
其中有些分类任务很有难度
We'll be exploring two main ways to separate this data
我们会探索两种主要方法来分离数据
by programming explicit rules that separate data into groups,
一种是编写明确规则 把数据分组
or by machine learning techniques that can automatically separate this data.
另一种是通过机器学习技巧 自动分类数据
Both approaches can be used to build an image classifier.
两种方法都能用于构建图像分类器
So what exactly is an image classifier?
那么 图像分类器究竟是什么？
An image classifier is an algorithm that takes in an image as
图像分类器是一种算法 可以输入图像
input and outputs a label or class that identifies that image.
然后输出一个识别图像的标签或类
For example, one type of classifier used in self driving cars will look at
例如 无人驾驶车中使用的一种分类器会查看
different images of roads and be able to identify whether that road contains humans,
不同的道路图像 并能识别道路上是否有人
cars, bikes and so on distinguishing and classifying each image based on its contents.
汽车、自行车等等 根据图像内容识别并分类图像
And there are many types of classifiers used to
还有很多类型的分类器
recognize specific objects or even behaviors,
可以识别具体的对象 甚至是行为
like whether a person is walking or running.
比如 某人是在行走还是跑步
But all these classifiers involve a similar series of steps.
但所有这些分类器的步骤都比较类似
I'll refer to these steps as part of the image classification pipeline.
我把这些步骤称作图像分类流程的一部分
First, a computer receives visual input from an imaging device like a camera.
首先 计算机从摄影设备 如摄像机 接受视觉输入
This is typically captured as an image or a sequence of images.
通常为一幅图像或特定顺序的一系列图像
Each image is then sent through
每个图像都经历
some pre-processing steps whose purpose is to standardize each image.
一些预处理步骤 对其进行归一化处理
Common pre-processing steps include resizing an image or rotating it to change its shape,
常见的预处理步骤包括调整图像大小、旋转改变形状
or transforming the image from one color to another like from color to gray scale.
或把图像从一种颜色转换为另一种颜色 比如 从彩色变为灰阶
Only by standardizing each image, for example,
只有当所有图像都归一化后
and making them the same size can you then
比如 调整为同样大小后 你才能够
compare them and further analyze them in the same way.
使用同样的方法对比图像并进一步分析
Next, we extract features.
接下来 我们提取特征
Features are what help us define certain objects and they're
特征可以帮助我们定义某些对象
usually information about object, shape or color.
它们通常是关于对象、形状或颜色的信息
Some features that distinguish a car from a bicycle are that a car is
一些把汽车和自行车区分开的特征是
usually a much larger shape and it has four wheels instead of two.
汽车往往形状较大 而且有四个轮子 而不是两个轮子
The shape and wheels would be distinguishing features for a car,
形状和轮子数量就是汽车的区分特征
and we'll talk more about features later in this lesson.
本课后面部分我们会详细讨论特征
And finally, these features are fed into
最后 这些特征馈入
a classification algorithm also referred to as a model that classifies the image.
一个分类算法 也叫做一个模型 对图像进行分类
This step looks at any features from
这一步会观察前一步中的任何特征
the previous step and predicts whether say this image is of a car,
并预测图像内容是汽车
or a pedestrian, or a bike and so on.
或行人、自行车等等
You'll be programming each of
你需要手动编写这些
these classification steps manually so that you really understand each step,
分类步骤的程序 保证你真正了解每个步骤
and by the end of this lesson you'll have
本课结束时 你将掌握
all the skills you'll need to complete the final project,
所有相关方法 可以顺利完成最终的实战项目
building a traffic light classifier,
你将能够构造一个交通灯分类器
which takes in images of traffic lights and separates them into three classes,
它能够输入交通灯图像 并将其分为三类
red, yellow or green lights.
红灯、黄灯或绿灯